I will buy an AC from the recycling bins in March 2024.
The name of that AC is what makes the marquee stand out
.  So, if you come here and
see the rate of this 1.510 3 star AC,
then it is 28990. When
I buy this AC,
I also come and
buy this package.  That's what Complete Appliance
Protection is all about. If
you look at the rate for three years, it's
1599. If you're wondering if
there's a Complete Appliance Protection or not,
who can offer this for three years, then One
Assist is a
company that can do that.  So, I got the invoice for that
.  If you look at the plan start date, it
says March 9, 2024.  The plan mentions that the end date is
March 8, 2027
.  When I
bought the AC, the only thing on my mind was
whether this AC would run or not, whether it would leak or not.
I didn't
plan for 10 or 15 years.
That means we buy our AC on a tight budget
.  I bought
this three-year appliance
protection with the idea that it would last me for three or four years.  I had come and bought this package with the additional amount, believing that even if
we didn't have any problems for three years,
they would still take care of it
.  The AC was also running great and
without any problems. We
recently posted a video
saying that we are servicing the AC, and the
reason for that was that the AC's cooling seemed to be
a bit lacking
.  So we said we could do the service and
did a complete service.
Why are we going to put our hands on it if it's running well?  The
rule with electronics is that if
something is working well, you
should never touch it or disturb it.  So I
can live with that kind of idea.  So, if that's the case, I had it
serviced because it was a bit lacking in cooling.  It was a little
better then, but at the same time,
it felt like there was a cooling problem somewhere.  But the cooling doesn't
come and go completely.  We would have checked our
thermometer and
wondered.  The cooling
was just coming.  But it feels like there's a little bit of a gap
.  Okay, so I thought maybe there was a gas
leak, so I
went upstairs and checked to see if it
was in the evaporation coil or not, and there was a
light ice formation that kept coming
.  So
I knew that the case was coming and that it was a scam.
We have been paying for this case bill, and we have been covering the AC for
three years. If
that is the case, they will
cover us with the Complete Appliance Protection. In
the hope that on 21/42026,
that is, on April 21, I
came to One Assist, installed it, and then
booked a service call.
Then, that same day, a technician from One Assist
called.  Hello,
hello,
you said it was AC, Mark. Yes,
yes,
what's wrong?   Cooling
gas is coming.
Cooling gum is coming.
We are reading the warranty if you have made additional candy.
How can you say "yes, yes" so much?   It's
coming, but I think there will
be a shortage of gas like there is now
.
And the app itself showed me
the option to schedule a visit.  So
the data was not available until the 25th,
so I
scheduled a technician visit for the 25th
.  In the meantime,
I think a sister called and said that she was from One Assist and that she was in the area service team.
They called and asked what the problem was and
all those kinds of details
.  I gave it too.  On the 25th, on the
date mentioned, the technician
came and inspected the gas. He said that the
problem was gas. I
had already told him on the phone. So, if there was a gas
problem, he came with the gas
cylinder in his hand
.  And not only that, the
technician brother who came over also came and
followed us.  So he came and praised us so much, and
then came upstairs and
hammered in all that insulation,
so I thought he'd appreciate that too
.  But the driver spat and
left.
I was also admiring something about you
.
This
will not improve cooling at all.  They made you look
bad by saying that you must have had a gas leak because you had a gas leak.  Then
the brother came and called the One Assist
sister and said, "This kind of
case is a problem, so
I brought it
."  But what did that sister
say? No, you shouldn't
change everything so easily.  I need to come and protect you a little
.  This means that you can only come and file the case after
getting approval from our company
.  That's why you didn't do the film, he
said.  Then
that sister came and called me.   They
called and asked if there were any cases like this
.
I already knew that,
that's why he brought it to fill the case
.  If they tell you to do it
,
no, that's not possible.
Okay, sir.  Because
we are ready only after we get approval
.
We can come and send an email, get approval, and only then
ask them to file a case.  Okay,
how long will it take for approval?
It will take one day.
Okay, let them get their company's procedure approved and do it
.  I said that I wasn't going to lose much weight after just a
day or two, so
I gave up.   In
the meantime, they came and asked me to send them a
360° video of Asia, covering all sides
.  They asked if
the video of the indoor unit below and the video of the outdoor unit in
between were too high
.  Is this all a question of
where we can get our feet wet after Asia?
The question seems to be a bit of a question.
Then
you will see a sticker on the outdoor unit.  Why is it a problem that the sticker doesn't stick
?  If the company itself is just
sitting there,
what can I do about it?  They asked me to take a photo of that sticker and
send it.  Even if I say no, they won't
believe me.
They only admit that there are no stickers after sending a 360° video.  They said they would get approval in two days, but they called
two
days later.
What do you say when you call me? Is it
approved?
Sir, I have a video of our case. I don't get approval. I
think I got it.
I will let you know.
Okay, they
called to update the approval.  Because it's been two days, is
n't it? That's why they said to update it
.  This is a
good thing.  They dropped
a big bombshell on me, saying that they would get approval on the 28th
.
They say that our case is not covered by the policy you took out, sir.
What do you mean?   The
policies we have taken out do not cover the case.
I didn't select anything specific like that and then
all that policy came and
sucked me in.  Full Coverage Complete
Appliance Protection was the only option
.  I selected only that and
ordered it.   It's
detected, sir.  Would you like to
speak to customer care once and
get on the line?
Which number is customer care?   Just type the
One Assist customer care number into Google
Chrome and it will come up.  Then
contact them and
tell them that they are saying that
.
Aren't you one assist?  They
ended up saying that they wouldn't be able to cover it simply.  I
asked for it by mail.  Don't even give me the email.  They told me to call One Aces
customer care and ask
.
We said okay and called their customer care.  But when we call, the
recorded voice
goes into repeat mode and no
agent is there to answer the call.
Come to One Assist
Complete Protection for Your Apps.
I came through the One Assist app and
booked this service.  Okay, I checked to see if I could
get any help through the app, and
that chat support was there.
This app was also updated with this bot
.  They mentioned things like what
status the spare parts are in and when they should
arrive
.  After I came and
told them that I needed to talk to an agent,
an agent called Sokana came and connected me.
Then I asked, "What does the executive say if my AC comes and
has full coverage? If so, then a claim
from One Assets comes in and gets
rejected, a
claim for a gas comes in and gets rejected, and they
mention it like that." I had mentioned that
.
What did that mother say?
Your AC needs gas charging.
This service came and mentioned something like that, but it's
not in your current plan
.  So I asked, "What is my current
plan and what is its name?"
Flipkart Complete Appliance Production has
mentioned this amount for a 3-year plan on an air conditioner.  And in the very bottom of the
page, the Ibermesh had
mentioned that if you had read the terms and conditions, you would know that your case would not be covered.
Oh, okay, I've read the terms and
conditions, so
I'll come and look for the terms and
conditions.  So these are
our terms and conditions.  So if
you look at the bottom of this, it has been
mentioned that one case top-up in 3 years. This can be
claimed in the second and third year.  That is,
why is there no first year? If so,
is the first year covered by the brand's warranty or not? So, only the second and third years
are covered as an extended warranty.  So they mentioned that it would cover the second and
third years
.  We're in our third year, so it's only during that time
.  So I
took a screenshot of it and
sent it to my sister.  I will escalate this to the Area Service
Manager
.
That sister
had said something like that, "They will come and proceed."  I asked, "What's wrong with my plan?
How can you tell me that you won't be covered without checking properly?"
Then I
came to it and it was
lying there, rolling around in a terrible mess.  Okay, if you ask when you will come and
fill the case,
we will come and fill the case for you within 24 to 48 hours.
If you ask what happens if it's late, they'll mention something like, "
We'll take another 24 hours
."
Because what they said was that the date came and
I spoke on the 28th.  They
came on the 28th and asked for two days' time.   The
second day, the 30th,
has arrived.  I still haven't received the case, so I
said, "Okay, let's reach out to that sister and ask her."
We went to chat support and asked her,
but then they
started from the beginning again.  Sir, they are telling me again that the
case will not be covered under your plan
.
After sending the screenshot of the terms and conditions again, what are they doing? If so,
come to the stand-alone maintenance service and refill the gas, it
will not be covered. They have said that functional repairs, such as gas
charging, are absolutely covered
.
I asked, "What did I call you, brother? Dust off the dust and go, and bring the case with you."
Cooling is not working properly.  Come and
see it.  So this
comes in the functional repair account.
Then, when the gas charging arrives and the bill is paid,
I'll send a technician after telling you all these things.  I'll send the technician over with the
correct input
.  I went to the area service manager and
asked him to make this a priority, and they kept rolling it like that
.  Now this person comes to the app and
tells the area service manager again that he will fill the gas tank and tell them that
?  Then when
they send an approval email, it
gets rejected.  This is the problem.
What did I do after I said okay?
Then I'll send the terms and conditions by email
.
I
sent the terms and conditions by email, saying that you should check the email and reply to me by email.
After sending the email, the Senior
Relationship Manager, the Dedicated Case
Officer, and all of them left a message saying that they would assign everything and
complete your case within 24 to 48 hours
.   Should
I give this chat experience a five-star rating?  Clipping.   On
the second of May, I received a phone call
.  Someone like that
came and called.  He
said that he will handle this case from now on. Good afternoon, this is mean. Work on your
case until not. So
what is he saying? If so,
two companies are involved here.
One came and the other came.
Flipkart. So, we can only get
approval from those two companies to
come and
bill our case.
Because like different companies, okay, we need to contact
Flipkart in this. We need to take the difference. It might take some time. Okay, how much time will it take? If
you ask, it will take a
maximum of one week.
That is the maximum. We will
not let it take that long. However, I am telling you this as a
reference. He
said that and said that it will take a week. But this is the max.
Okay, we will also wait a week.
So, let's take a video.  I would have been
taking a video of the explosion, and there's a chance
you've seen a few shots, but in the
meantime, that
sister made another call.  Let's make a call and
close like we did in the old days
.  I'll book a call for you soon
.  Because this is going to be different.   Will
you book a recall once you have received approval from Flipkart after this call is closed
?   They
said, "If you tell me those eight OTPs, I'll close it and leave."   If
you gave me the OTP, I will close it now
.
Then I said, "As
long as it doesn't solve the problem for me, I won't."
How many company approvals do you
need?  I couldn't handle the problem,
so I told my dad I would
n't drink
.  What I'm asking is, my
case is still open and my
issue hasn't been closed yet, so I'm not
accepting anything.
My point is that you shouldn't cancel or close the case.
Why are they closing this? If so, what if there is a
problem tomorrow? In
that case, will it
show as if it has been pending for a long time? Will it show as if it has been pending for more than 10 days?
Otherwise, they will just close this case and
open a new case.
Look, we came and
closed this case within a week.
And not only that, they will also
use it for marketing.
Look at all the tickets we booked, we closed them all within a week
.  No, we
closed the case within two days.
That case will not be closed because of such a mention.
Even if they do, they will close it as they
wish. On the sixth
day, they will come back and call you again. They will call you and book
you a new call like this. When
your area service manager
makes a request for a case again, it
will be rejected. You
will not find all that. You will come and
tell them. You will receive
a separate email like that. After the email comes,
you will have to pay the bill for that case.
That is what they will
tell me
and suppose if anyone from me anyone is injured
that is not covered, simply inform them that your case is handled by the escalation department
and in the terms and conditions are mion so
gas is covered
so do not close the compil
once again to the relevant that
is covered and do not close this
complaint without informing
What should I tell the local card that called me when I came here? Sister, don't
rush, don't
send an email, come and wait,
you will get an email,
then do this for me, and
tell me something like that. It's a great
service. Just like I said, on the seventh
day, I got a phone call again
from that sister. That
sister came again and said that I will
send approval for the case
.  I told that sister,
you can send it yourself, but it will be
rejected again. You have to wait a
little while. You will receive an
email from another party. After that email
arrives,
you have to check it and cover it. That
customer care
communication department came in the middle and checked to see if
you had received any email. If
not, send an
email and ask for it.
Two days passed, three days passed, and a
week passed, as he said. On the ninth day, I
received another phone call.
I mean, we're close, sir, we're
very close to getting approval
.
Just wait until Monday.
They were saying that they would replace it immediately after approval.
You wait until Monday.
I'll have the technician
come and take a look when it's ready, okay?   We just did it to
wait.  I said, "We'll just do it
until Monday and get away with it," and
left.  The Monday they promised
arrived.  There is no
update.  On Tuesday, the
technician brother came and made a direct call
.
That AC gas is up,
that's what they called you and
told you to fill the gas.
So, they came and asked if you could come tonight.
I'm not home. Okay, no problem. Someone will
come and fill it. Okay, okay, no
problem. You send it now.
I won't be there. That's how it is.
My money will be there. They will be there. They will be there. They will be there. They will check this bank and do something
else. They will
come on Tuesday night and bill the gas and
close the service. Is there
a way to steal that money? It
started on the 21st of April and it was
completed on the 12th of May.  It took me
almost 21 days to do this
.  The ultimate
thing about this is that after 21 days of perfect
sunshine, when they lit the stove and
filled the gas, it
started raining from the stove.  What's going on here?
Even though you spent 30,000 and
bought an AC,
you decided to do it quickly this summer.
If that's the case, no
one can change that.  This whole
thing might seem simple to you if you watch the video
.  But only I know
how much I worked for this
.  I searched for all those terms and
conditions, downloaded that old email, and
before that, I
read the terms and conditions of the One Assist and the Complete Appliance Protection in full.
Then I took my terms
and conditions, searched them, and
saw if there was gas charging in them or not, and
sent them an email.
I must have talked to them for about 30 to 40 phone calls.
This is what I did, so I followed it up and tried it, and they
came to the case and filed it.
And I didn't even think about putting this in the table of contents
.  I didn't do it for that reason either.
I did it for my own needs.  Why would
we spend ₹2500 on filling the gas tank?
Then
why not
pay 1600 rupees for 4 years of appliance protection if it's not needed?
Isn't that a waste? So
I did it for that very reason.
What would they have done if they didn't know about it
?  Even if they were unaware or even
aware,
they would
n't take these steps to address so many things.  They would have left if they had said that they wouldn't cover it, whether it was a second or third
leg or not, when they talked to him
.
Leave Thembulla alone for all that.
No, they could not wait for those 21 days and would have
paid money to another yard and filed a case.
Or if there were people who did
not know how to check that much detail, they would have
thought that it would not be covered.
Even if they knew that it would be covered, they would have to
speak English, speak Hindi,
make him speak from Hindi to English,
and deal with the local weather.
How much work would it take to get communication from them and put it on this page?
This and this is the reality of
this kind of company today. They simply say that it will not be
covered for you and
then check it later and then
it will
be covered. Like that, we have to
do various things for it and then
we have to cover it.  And
many people ask me, "
Did you go looking for trouble or did trouble come looking for you?"
I don't
know.  But almost everything that comes into my life is like that
.  Even if it's a
joke, it's
hard to get inside.
When we encounter problems like this with every issue, it doesn't get to that level and it's not good.
Tell me yourself what I did wrong in this.  When I bought the AC, I paid for it
.  When
I asked for that three-year complete appliance protection, they said, "You
can select that option, so
I selected it properly and
paid for it." I bought it
.  So I did everything properly
.  There is
no mistake on my part.  Even then,
my services are being
denied and I
can't do anything about it.  It seems like a joke to spend our hard-earned
money and our lives on a
company like this
.
I've never seen a person born like you in my
life.
He included you too.   A
lot of people are messaging me too.
I bought this model on Flipkart.  I bought this on Amazon and was told that it had
a lot of problems
.  But I ca
n't do anything about it.
I can either come and
make a video like that or fight with them if I have evidence for something
.  Beyond that, if I
brought others to the table and fought with them,
then I already have problems like I said
.  So when it
comes to a problem, I might not be
able to prove that point.
I might get a tattoo for that.  So
that's why I can't respond to those kinds of messages
.  Even if everything is
right and we know everything, there will always be those who try to deceive
us
.  The
reason I post a video like this is
so that you can get some clarity.   Please
share the video as much as possible.   Please support
.  And
subscribe to the channel.  So it's the
support you can give that will
motivate us to the next level.
Thank you.